- Why?
- I do not know.
- Why do you speak Skåne?
It's incredible.
Because I can't cook and all the least moules fries.
So I called in professional chef Sofia Henriksson, who wanted to come and save me.
- Mind poor man, you should not cry.
-What?
It's just the onion.
- When you spent time with these scouts, how long did you hang?
Because I think it is so fascinating that you have learned a whole dialect.
- We had a dinner there and then we were there playing.
- And you've learned a whole dialect?
- Yes.
- Do you have it?
And he said yes.
- Yes.
- And you called him on your phone.
- On my toad.
- On your toad you called your dad and he said we can check?
- Yes.
- Okay.
Not 100% credible.
They drive ...
It is violence, it is violent.
But first we will try a job that is quite accurate on the Swedish average salary around 37,000.
- On the average salary we find ordinary professions such as advertisers, painters, aviation technicians and midwives.
So today I will release a child, what it seems.
I really don't know who gave me permission for this.
But now we drive.
- Many may wonder why not such a socially important job earns more.
The simple answer is that there is an established salary level for midwives set based on negotiations between trade unions and employers.
However, if it would turn out in the long run that not enough people are willing to work to the salary-
-Then there will be a shortage of midwives and then you will have to increase your salary eventually.
- Hello!
- Paula huh?
- Yes, welcome.
- Now you should come back.
- Have a good time.
Bye.
- I saw you on Youtube.
- Have you seen me on Youtube?
- Yes!
- Oh she has almost frozen.
- But heard the heart.
Now it is like this.
This is a birth bed.
So Mauri, now let's see here.
- What are you tanning about?
Nothing.
Do you think you ...
Now I step up behind.
Today's competitors are Hugo and Julia who have salary under minimum wage.
There Hugo steps into the office at the manager.
- A great talent.
Birth 02.
- There he asks the question.
- Clearly formulated.
- The question is out in the air, but the boss gestures denies!
There will be no increase in salary for Hugo.
- Healthy daring, but not the right tactics.
- Then we will see how it goes for his opponent Julia.
As in this now steps in.
But it will be a no from the manager.
But Julien picks up the phone.
What happens?
- Yes, she calls Handels.
- Damn what fun.
What a good news.
- It sure is!
- Yes.
And as new friends, Paula and I went and some of the other midwives on a little AW.
If one day I become a dad, I already know who the midwife should be.
A blonde, wonderful girl who laughs a lot and makes bad imitations of babies.
However, we will continue to the next job of 75,000 in monthly salary.
A profession that requires tremendous responsibility but also high intelligence and simultaneous ability.
It is a responsible job.
It requires education and that education is quite demanding.
At the same time, it is a pretty niche job.
There is a fairly small group of people who can be considered.
- Approximately.
Had this been the reality, they would probably have called later and asked what was happening.
- Is that so?
- Yes, yes, but they had.
- Tower Good Morning Air France 2063. Ils, Runway 01 Left.
- So send it first.
- I love that he who is a pilot also offers some dialects.
Now he was French.
Are you from French?
- oui, oui.
We from from France.
- You from France!
- Scandinacia 2293, Yankee 6.
We have some problems with our landing gear.
We are unnable to vacate the runway.
They don't have a lot of patience, pilots either.
- Scandinavia 006.
In sequence.
- Line up runway zero.
- Line Up, Line Away Zero, Left Turn Departure.
- No not yet.
You can't start it because you have an airplane in front.
- Now he goes!?
- Yes, now it is very serious here.
- No, no, no, no, no, no!
What is he doing?
- And you see that now you have one on the track too so now you have to ...
- Do not escape!
Soon it is time to work with one of the richest people in the Nordic region.
But first we will visit a job with a monthly salary around 150,000.
At this level over 100,000, there is only one percent of Sweden's population -
-As you earn more than that.
It is CEO, there are bank officials and a 19-year-old in Liljeholmen-
-As a few hours a day sits with his computer.
So this guy is called Neo.
That you have been surrounded by a guy named Neo in this team.
So then you start to grow old.
Hello!
- Well, neo.
Nice.
- Mauri!
Nice!
- Welcome.
- So here it has looked.
- And about what do you earn for a month?
- 150 ish.
- On sitting like that in your soft pants and just chilling.
- Short break for professions that earn worse than Neo.
Specialist doctors, managers within bank, managers in insurance,-
-Pilotes, brokers, ministers in the Swedish government ...
- It doesn't feel great.
- Why doesn't it feel good?
- Then it feels wrong in some way.
- No, do you get a bad conscience?
- Here I sit and what do I do?
I don't even have a high school diploma.
- Are you going to show me something?
- Yes, I'll show something.
- You then get a document every morning on how the hotels have gone the day before.
- Yes.
- And there you see this ...
In Milan it was 100% fully occupied.
- Milan?
- It's Clarion Arlanda.
We jump a little back and forth in time.
We take care of it.
You just need to go with.
Don't be afraid, Petter.
No problem.
You are 27 years old and tell me that I'm not afraid.
As if this was my first rodeo.
- You invite you to get a little bus with you.
- I love it.
I have no restrictions.
- No, it feels so.
- You can't resent me.
-Can not I?
- No, it's not possible.
- Should I test?
-Yes.
- How is the weather down there?
-It is quite good.
- It doesn't feel like I would go for me to make you sad.
- I cry lightly but it is for completely different reasons.
- Yes!
Didn't you know about it?
I can show you later.
- No.
- Love Actually.
The world's best film of all time.
- Because ... but what?
Then the darkness lay over Gothenburg where Petter would inaugurate his new hotel Draken.
- And we will be able to follow your entire work day tomorrow.
- Completely to the dragon wakes up.
- Yes, I look forward to that.
- Yes me too.
Sleep now.
He has a great potential for improvement.
- Where have you been my friend?
- How fast you were, have you already eaten?
- Yes but, how difficult can it be to shower?
Turn on the shower,-
-washing hair, finished, out.
- What does your schedule look like?
So how tight it is?
Oh!
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
Is it just today still?
- Yes.
- So the plan today, is it to inaugurate this new hotel in Gothenburg?
- And now you just go out and do a lot of pressure?
- Yes, should you keep up?
- All day!
- Take a puddle, stove puddle.
Have you attended three weeks of training at Kroki in Italy?
- Now I'm mad at you ...
- Why?
- You're so fucking cocky now over there.
- Now I am ready.
- Okay, you're totally useless.
- But you thought I had been on such a course for three weeks in Italy?
You believed in it?
- I believed in it!
- But why did you write fuck you, Petter?
- It was because I was so angry with you.
When I thought you had been on a crockery course.
- Why?
Oh no!
It was a blow under the belt.
- Was it?
And now it was time for the big inauguration of Petter's new hotels.
A grand show had been prepared for hundreds of invited guests.
But first Petter would go on the red carpet.
And he did it with a pale rush close behind.
- What should I say to pepper?
What can I help you with?
- You sat on the rope, what did you think?
- When you start driving it there, the second part of the song.
Have just started!
Yes there is something about this guy.
First of all, he is probably not a hotel owner or CEO.
He is a seller.
Petter Stordalen could have been able to sell syphilis to you and you had still bought it.
Above all, he is actually extremely charming, curious and in the name of honesty very cute.
He is also good at his job, however, it seems at least as strenuous and demanding to be a babysitter or midwife.
Although they get about 2300 times less paid.